<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Corbin Staaben</title><link>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Corbin Staaben</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 01:26:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Roguelike Tutorial - The beginning… and the end?</title><link>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/roguelike_tutorial_part_0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 01:26:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/roguelike_tutorial_part_0/</guid><description>Inspiration I’ve always had an interest in text-based games. It’s always felt like these games needed to be much more engaging than their graphically-gifted counterparts because there were fewer pretty things to look at. They had to engage your imagination, or at least your interest, to such an extent that you would continue to play. It originally started when I was learning that I was good at writing (for a small town high school student), and only grew the more I started using, and learning about, computers.</description></item><item><title>Comment policy</title><link>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/comment_policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 22:45:49 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/comment_policy/</guid><description>Welcome to my simple little site. The posts I make here will contain code, links to code, and thoughts about code and technology. I&amp;rsquo;m not omniscient and I certainly am not an expert in any field, so I&amp;rsquo;ve enabled comments on my posts to let any readers comment on the posts to provide corrections or findings of their own. The best environment for working in tech is a learning-friendly environment, I&amp;rsquo;ve found.</description></item><item><title>And so it begins...</title><link>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/and_so_it_begins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 22:24:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://cstaaben.github.io/blogs/and_so_it_begins/</guid><description>The beginning This is the begining of what I&amp;rsquo;m striving to continue running for quite some time. My initial reason for starting this was to hopefully get more interest from potential employers. After thinking about it some, I want to make it something more. I want this to be a place for discussion about programming, game development, tech news, whatever. A learning environment. The world is full of negativity, and if I can foster one little area of positivity, I will.</description></item></channel></rss>